Texted
the wrong
guy
Now I'm
having coffee
OK
so picture
this
It's a
Thursday
night
and I'm
completely
trashed
at this
college
party
right
My friend
dares
me to
text my
crush something
crazy
and
I'm like
why not
So I
text
him
hey
can't
stop thinking
about
your dog's
Instagram
I wake
up the
next morning
with
zero
memory
and
a cringy
response
from
him
I don't
have a
dog
but want
to grab
coffee
I cringe
so
hard
but think
maybe
this
could work
I show
up to
coffee
and
guess what
His twin
brother
happens
to
own a
dog dedicated
account
and yep
they swapped
phones
last
night
Talk
about swapping
places
Now I'm
sitting there
dining
with
a dude
who's
annoyed
at the
mix-up
but surprisingly
interested
How
did that
happen