Curtain
Toga
Confessions
So I'm
standing
on the
quad
absolutely
drenched
in
glitter
and
wearing
a toga
made out
of my
roommate's
curtains
when
my ex
walks
up
like
Are you
serious
It all
started
with a
wild
night
at the
frat
house
Cheap
tequila
bad decisions
you know
the drill
Somehow
a
game of
truth or
dare
turned
into
me stealing
the
dean's
goldfish
thinking it
was a
genius plan
to get
his attention
By 2am
I
was marching
through
campus
chanting my
sorority's
anthem
and
waving the
fishbowl
like it was
the Olympic
torch
Everything
went
south
when
I realized
I
accidentally
texted
my
ex our
entire
group
chat
complete
with
me confessing
I still
thought
he was
cute
Well
you know
wearing
a curtain
toga
Just as
he's reading
the texts
campus
security
rolls
up
because
apparently
stealing
the
dean's
beloved
fish
qualifies
as
Grand
Theft
Aquatic
Anyway
now I
have a
beautiful
overlapping
start
to
a court
summons
and an
unexpected
reunion
with
the guy
I
may
be still
kind
of like
What
a night