I met Mack set a laundromat because he tried to rescue my pink sock from eternal spin-cycle
doom.
We started texting memes and dumb TikTok trends back and forth, then hooking up between
half-folded sheets and pizza boxes.
I swore he was different, not just another smooth-talking charmer, until I found out he and
my roommate, Tiff, had been DMing heart emojis behind my back.
When I caught them swapping more than detergent, I posted screenshots of their cringe messages
to our group chat with the caption, dirty laundry, but make it public.
Tiff moved out, Mack's ghosted everyone, and the building called me Queen of the Spin
Cycle for a week.
Now I do my laundry in peace.
And my socks?
They never go missing.